Guide to the Miscellaneous human sexuality periodicals,circa 1950-2003
Miscellaneous human sexuality periodicals,circa 1950-2003
- Jamaica Gaily News (Box 4)
  Publication Country: Jamaica
  Publication City: Kingston
- Joker (Box 4)
  Subject: Gay, Entertainment, Alternative local newspaper, 1970s
  Publisher: Random Louse
- Journal of Law and Policy (Brooklyn Law School) (Box 4)
  Subject: Families, Gay, Lesbian, Legal, 1990s
  Publisher: Brooklyn Law School
- Journal of Sex Education & Therapy (Box 4)
  Subject: Education, Therapy, Psychology, Health, 1980s
  Publisher: American Association of Sex Educators, Counselors and Therapists (AASECT)
- Journal, The (Lesbian & Gay Caucus, California Democratic Party) (Box 4)
  Subject: Politics, Gay, Lesbian, 1980s
  Publisher: Lesbian & Gay Caucus California Democratic Party
  Publication City: West Los Angeles, CA
- Just for the Record (Box 4)
  Subject: Directory, Mass media, Television, Gay, Lesbian, 1990s
  Publisher: New Orleans Gay and Lesbian Television Show
- Just For You (JFY) (Box 4)
  Subject: People of Color, Gay male, Entertainment, 1990s
  Publisher: Be Open Corporation
- Keeping In Touch (Box 5)
  Subject: Religious, Gay, Lesbian, 1980s
  Publisher: Universal Fellowship of Metropolitan Community Churches
- Key West (Box 5)
  Subject: Directory, Travel, Cruising, Gay
  Publisher: The Key West Business Guild
  Publication City: Key West, FL
- Kinship Connection (Seventh Day Adventists [SDA]) (Box 5)
  Subject: Religious: Seventh-day Adventist, Gay, Lesbian, 1980s
  Publisher: Seventh-day Adventist Gays and Lesbians and Their Friends
- Kitchen Table: Women of Color Press (Box 5)
  Subject: Literary, Catalog, Women, Books, People of Color, Lesbian, Feminist, 1980s
  Publisher: Women of Color Press
  Publication City: Latham, NY
- Kontakt-zone (German Language) (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Entertainment, Comics
  Publisher: PRINT SERVICE (Beilsteiner Str., Berlin)
- Ladies for the 80's (Box 5)
  Subject: Women, 1980s
  Publisher: Ladies for the 80's LTD, Inc.
  Publication City: Oaklyn, NJ
- LAGAR (Lesbian And Gay Archives Roundtable [now known as: InQueeries]) (Box 5)
  Subject: Occupation Based Organizations, Books, History, Gay, Lesbian, Cornell University
  Publisher: Society of American Archives' Lesbian And Gay Archives Roundtable
- LAGUAR (Lesbians and Gays United Against Repression) (Box 5)
  Subject: Lesbian, Gay, Gay liberation movement, Politics, 1980s
  Publisher: Lesbians And Gays United Against Repression (LAGUAR)
- Lambda (The Bisexual, Gay Men, Lesbians, and Allies for Diversity Newsletter) (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, College/University, Gender issues
  Publisher: B-GLAD (office of UNC-Chapel Hill)
  Publication City: Chapel Hill, NC
- Lambda Archives of San Diego (Formerly Lesbian and Gay Historical Society of San Diego) (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, History
  Publisher: Lambda Archives of San Diego
- Lambda Calendar (Ithaca Lesbian Gay Bisexual Transgender Task Force) (Box 5)
  Subject: Calendar, Community, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Family, Transgender, Cornell University, 2000s
  Publisher: Ithatca Lesbian Gay Bisexual Transgender Task Force
  Publication City: Ithaca, NY
- Lambda Circle News (Box 5)
  Subject: News, Gay, 1980s, Alternative local newspaper, Lesbian
  Publication City: Albany, NY
- Lambda Letter, The (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender, Community, 1990s, News
  Publisher: The Lambda Group, Inc.
  Publication City: Baton Rouge, LA
- Lambda Letters, The (Box 5)
  Subject: 1970s, Gay, Lesbian, News, Community, Gay liberation movement
  Publisher: P.R.I.D.E. of Lambda, Inc.
  Publication City: Cedar Rapids, IA
- Lambda Liaison (Newsletter of Lambda Alliance) (Box 5)
  Subject: 1980s, Gay, Lesbian, News, Community
  Publisher: Lambda Alliance (New Jersey)
  Publication City: Eatontown, NJ
- Lambda Line (News for Brooklyn Lesbians & Gay Men From Lambda Independent Democrats, Brooklyn's Lesbian & Gay Political Club) (Box 5)
  Subject: Lesbian, Gay, Politics, News, HIV/AIDS, Legal, Gay liberation movement, 1990s
  Publisher: Lambda Independent Democrats
- Lambda Louisville News (Box 5)
  Subject: 1980s, Gay, Lesbian, News, Alternative local newspaper
  Publisher: Lambda Louisville, Inc.
  Publication City: Louisville, KY
- Lambda Pages (Dallas-Fort Worth) (Box 5)
  Subject: Directory, Gay, Lesbian, 1990s
  Publisher: Lambda Republic, Inc.
  Publication City: Dallas, TX
- Lambda Times (The Newsletter of Lubbock Lesbian/Gay Alliance) (Box 5)
  Subject: 1990s, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: Lubbock Lesbian/Gay Alliance
  Publication City: Lubbock, TX
- Lambda, The (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay liberation movement, Gay, Lesbian, 1970s
  Publisher: Central Jersey G.A.A.
- Lambda, The (Gay Sports in New York) (Box 5)
  Publisher: The Lambda
  Publication City: Village Station, NY
- Lavender Health (Office of Gay & Lesbian Health Concerns, New York City Department of Health) (Box 5)
  Subject: Health, Government Publication(s), Gay, Lesbian, HIV/AIDS, 1980s
  Publisher: Office of Gay & Lesbian Health Concerns, New York City Department of Health
- Lavender Labor (The Newsletter for Lesbian/Gay Loabor Activists and Supporters) (Box 5)
  Subject: Labor, Occupation Based Organizations, Gay, Lesbian, 1990s
  Publisher: Lavender Labor
  Publication City: Oakland, CA
- Lavender Lambda (Geneseo Gay Freedom Coalition, SUNY at Geneseo) (Box 5)
  Subject: 1970s, Gay, Gay liberation movement, College/University, Lesbian, Heterosexuality
  Publisher: Geneseo Gay Freedom Coalition
  Publication City: Geneseo, NY
- Lavender Special, The (A Newsletter Serving the Alfred Gay Community) (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, News
  Publication City: Alfred, NY
- Lavender Umbrella (Box 5)
  Subject: 1980s, Lesbian, Feminist, Women
  Publisher: Lavender Umbrella
  Publication City: Kansas City, MO
- LAW (Lesbian Alumnae of Wellesley Newsletter) (Box 5)
  Subject: College/University, Lesbian
  Publisher: Lesbian Alumnae of Wellesley
- Leap Leap: Shameless Hussy Review (Box 5)
  Subject: Literary, Feminist, Women
  Publisher: Shameless Hussy Press
  Publication City: San Lorenzo, CA
- Leather Pride! (Box 5)
  Subject: s/m, Leather, Pride Parade and Events, 1990s, Gay
  Publisher: Leather Pride Project
- Leatherfolk Connection, The (United Leatherfolk of Connecticut) (Box 5)
  Subject: Leather, 1990s, Fetish, Gay
  Publisher: United Leatherfolk of Connecticut
  Publication City: Hartford, CT
- Legacy (Later known as "Our Legacy") (An Uncommon Legacy Foundation, Inc.) (Box 5)
  Subject: Lesbian, Women
  Publisher: An Uncommon Legacy Foundation, Inc.
- Lesbian & Gay Health (Box 5)
  Publisher: (National Gay Health Education Foundation)
- Lesbian & Gay Health (National Gay Health Education Foundation) (Box 5)
- Lesbian and Gay Directory of Services and Resources (New York Metropolitan Area) (Box 5)
  Subject: Directory, Community service, Pride Parade and Events, Government Publication(s), Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: The New York City Office of the Comptroller
- Lesbian and Gay Labor Network (Box 5)
  Subject: Labor, Occupation Based Organizations, Lesbian, Gay, Community service, 1980s, 1990s
  Publisher: Lesbian and Gay Labor Network
- Lesbian and Gay News (Bloomington Gay and Lesbian Alliance) (Box 5)
  Subject: 1980s, Gay, Lesbian, News
  Publisher: Bloomington Gay and Lesbian Alliance
- Lesbian and Gay Pink Pages, The (Chicago) (Box 5)
  Subject: Directory, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: D.A.C. Marketing, Inc.
- Lesbian and Gay Pink Pages, The (Northwest) (Box 5)
- Lesbian Health Issues Newsletter (National Center for Lesbian Rights) (Box 5)
  Subject: Lesbian, Health, 1990s, Women
  Publisher: National Center for Lesbian Rights (NCLR)
- Lesbian Mothers' Resource Network (LMRN) (Box 5)
  Subject: Parenting, Lesbian, Families, Women, Pride Parade and Events, 1990s
  Publisher: Lesbian Mothers' Resource Network (LMRN)
- Lesbian Uprisings (Box 5)
- Lesbian/Gay Community Service Center of Greater Cleveland (LGCSCGC Annual Report '98) (Box 5)
  Subject: Lesbian, Gay, 1990s, Bisexual, HIV/AIDS, Transgender, Community service
  Publisher: The Lesbian/Gay Community Service Center of Greater Cleveland (LGCSCGC)
- Lesbian/Gay History Researchers Network Newsletter (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, History, Occupation Based Organizations, 1980s
  Publisher: Lesbian Heritage/D.C.
- Lesbian/Gay Rights Lobby of Texas (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Gay liberation movement, Legal, Politics, 1980s
  Publisher: Lesbian/Gay Rights Lobby of Texas
- Lesbians & Gays at Penn (News from) (Box 5)
  Subject: College/University, University of Pennsylvania, Gays, Lesbians, News, 1980s
  Publisher: Lesbians & Gays at Penn (LGAP)
- Lesbians in Colorado (Box 5)
  Subject: Lesbian, 1990s
  Publisher: Lesbians in Colorado
- Lespress (German Language) (Box 5)
  Subject: Lesbian, Entertainment, 2000s
  Publisher: Druckerei Paffenholz
- Letters from Camp Rehoboth (Box 5)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Gay, Lesbian, Community, Heterosexual, Community services
  Publisher: Camp Rehoboth, Inc.
  Publication City: Rehoboth Beach, DE
- LFOC Newsletter (Lesbian Feminist Organizing Committee) (Box 5)
  Subject: Lesbian, Feminist, 1980s, Women
  Publisher: Lesbian Feminist Organizing Committee (LFOC)
- LGAU: Newsletter of the Lesbian/ Gay Academic Union of Greater Cincinnati (Box 5)
  Subject: Education, College/University, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: The Lesbian/Gay Academic Union of Greater Cincinnati
- LGBC News (Newsletter of the Ontario NDP Lesbian, Gay & Bixexual Committee) (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Politics, News, 1990s
  Publisher: Onatio NDP Lesbian, Gay & Bisexual Committee
- LGLC Newsletter (Libertarians for Gay and Lesbian Concerns) (Box 5)
  Subject: News, Gay, Lesbian, Politics
  Publisher: Libertarians for Gay and Lesbian Concerns
- Liberation and Marxism (Box 5)
  Subject: Lesbian, Gay, Transgender, 1990s, Book reviews, Politics, Military
  Publisher: WW Publishers
- Liberation! (Gay Academic Union of Florida Atlantic University) (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Education, College/University, Politics, Pride Parade and Events, News
  Publisher: Gay Academic Union of Florida Atlantic University
  Publication City: Boca Raton, FL
- Libertine Magazine (The International Gay Advertiser) (Box 5)
  Subject: Cruising, Gay, Classifieds
  Publisher: Libertine Publishing
- Liberty (American Civil Liberties Union [ACLU] of Oklahoma) (Box 5)
  Subject: Politics, Legal, Gay liberation movement, Gay, Lesbian, 1980s
  Publisher: American Civil Liberties Union of Oklahoma (ACLU)
  Publication City: Oklahoma City, OK
- Liberty for All (LAMBDA Legal Defense and Education Fund, Inc.) (Box 5)
  Subject: Politics, Legal, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender, HIV/AIDS, 1980s
  Publisher: LAMBDA Legal Defense and Education Fund, Inc.
- Life Line (Lesbian and Gay Seventh-Day Adventists) (Box 5)
  Subject: Religious, Religious: Seventh-day Adventists, Gay, Lesbian, College/University, Families, Transsexual
  Publisher: Orion Fellowship Alliance, Inc.
- Life Style: A Lesbian and Gay Magazine (Box 5)
  Subject: Lesbian, Gay, Entertainment
  Publisher: Life Style A Lesbian & Gay Magazine
- Lighthouse, The (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, 1980s,
  Publisher: Lesbians And Gaymen of Saint John, Inc. (LAGOSJ)
  Publication City: Saint John, NB
- Link: The Interactive College Magazine (Box 5)
  Subject: College/University, Heterosexual, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual
  Publisher: Creative Media Generations
  Publication City: Englewood, NJ
- Literatussi (German Language) (Box 5)
  Publisher: Buchladen Mannerschwan GmbH
  Publication City: Hamburg
- Living Beyond the Closet (Box 5)
  Subject: 1990s, Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender, Legal, Families
  Publisher: Beyond the Closet
  Publication City: Bend, OR
- Living HIV (Box 5)
  Publisher: National Association of People with AIDS (NAPWA)
- LLEGO Informacion (Spanish and English Language) (Box 5)
  Subject: Latina/Latino, Gay, Lesbian, Politics, 1980s
  Publisher: Latino/a Lesbian y Gay Organization
- Log, The (The Newsletter of the Log Cabin Club) (Box 5)
  Subject: Politics, Gay, Lesbian, 1980s, Legal
  Publisher: Log Cabin Club
- Logomotive (A Magazine of Sex & Fun [from a bisexual perspective]) (Box 5)
  Subject: Bisexual, Entertainment, Zine, 1990s
- London Lesbian & Gay Film Festival (17th Annual) (Box 5)
  Subject: Entertainment, 2000s, Gay, Lesbian, Queer, Bisexual, Transgender, Intersex
  Publisher: The British Film Institute
  Publication City: London
- Los Angeles Dispatch (Box 5)
  Subject: News, 1980s, Lesbian, Gay, Pride Parade and Events, HIV/AIDS
  Publisher: Lambda Press, Inc.
- Lovetann (Norwegian Language) (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Entertainment, 1990s
- LRC Community News (Lesbian Resource Center) (Box 5)
  Subject: Lesbian, Women, News
  Publisher: Lesbian Resource Center (Pacific Women's Resources)
- Lutherans Concerned (Box 5)
  Subject: Religious: Lutheran, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual
  Publisher: Lutherans Concerned
- Lutherans Concerned (Toronto) (Box 5)
  Publisher: Lutherans Concerned (Toronto)
- Lutherans Concerned Michigan Newsletter (Box 5)
  Subject: Religious: Lutheran, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, 1980s
  Publisher: Lutherans Concerned Michigan
  Publication City: Ann Arbor, MI
- Made in Gay America (Box 5)
  Subject: Catalog, 1990s, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: Made in Gay America
  Publication City: Roanoke, VA
- Madison Edge, The (Box 5)
  Subject: News, Alternative local newspaper, Lesbian, Comics
  Publisher: Edge Cooperative
- Magazine, Le (French Language) (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, 1990s, Alternative local newspaper
  Publisher: Imprimerie Saint-Romuald
  Publication City: Quebec, QC
- Maine Lesbian Feminist Newsletter (Box 5)
  Subject: Lesbian, Feminist, 1980s
  Publisher: Maine Lesbian Feminist Community
  Publication City: Belfast, ME
- Mainliners (Box 5)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, 1990s
  Publisher: Mainliners, Ltd.
- Making a Difference (Quarterly Newsletter of the National Association of Lesbian and Gay Gerontologists) (Box 5)
  Subject: Aged, Gay, Lesbian, Occupation Based Organizations
  Publisher: The National Association of Lesbian and Gay Gerontologists
- Malepak (Box 5)
  Subject: Catalog, Gay, 1980s
  Publisher: Malepak
- Maluhia Me Ka Pono (Peace with Justice) Newsletter (Box 5)
  Subject: 1990s, Gay liberation movement
  Publisher: American Friends Service Committee-Hawai'i Area Program
- Man to Man (The Stag Magazine) (Box 5)
  Subject: Heterosexual, 1950s, Transgender, Transvestite, Men
  Publisher: Picture Magazines, Inc.
- Manifesto: Gay News for the Monterey Bay (The Non-heterosexual Newspaper of the Monterey Bay) (Box 5)
  Subject: News, Alternative local newspaper, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender, 2000s
  Publisher: Manifesto
  Publication City: Watsonville, CA
- Manitoba Gay Directory (Box 5)
- Mannerspiegel (German Language) (Box 5)
  Subject: News, Gay, Families
  Publisher: PRO FAMILIA Gesellschaft fur Sexualberatung und Familienplanunge
  Publication City: Frankfurt
- Mariposa Newsletter, The (Box 5)
  Subject: History, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender, Heterosexual, 1980s
  Publisher: Mariposa Education & Research Foundation
- Mark Tours North American Gay Hotel Guidebook (Box 5)
  Subject: Travel, Gay, Directory, 1980s
  Publisher: Mark Tours & Travel International, Inc.
- Massachusettes Gay & Lesbian Political Caucus (MGLPC) Newsletter (Box 5)
- Matrix: A Place of Our Own (Box 5)
  Publisher: MATRIX
- MCT: Mishpocheh (The Gay Sinagogue of Washington, D.C.) (Box 5)
  Subject: Religious: Jewish, Gay, Lesbian, 1970s
  Publisher: Mishpocheh of Washington, D.C.
- Media Action (from AIDS Committee of Toronto) (Box 5)
- Media Monitor (Gay & Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation/Denver) (Box 5)
  Subject: Mass media, Gay, Lesbian, Gay liberation movement, Politics, 1990s
  Publisher: Gay & Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation/ Denver
- Medical Alert (The National Organization of People with AIDS) (Box 5)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Politics, Health, Medicine, 1990s
  Publisher: The National Association of People with AIDS
- Men's Health (Box 5)
  Publisher: Rodale Press
  Publication City: Emmaus, PA
- Mentor (Oregon Resource for Men) (Box 5)
  Subject: Gender issues, News, Men, 1990s
  Publisher: Mentor
- Met Personals (Box 5)
  Subject: Entertainment, Classifieds, Heterosexual, Gay, 1980s
  Publisher: M.E.T. Publishing, Inc.
- Metamorphosis Theater (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay arts, Gay, African-American, Race
- Metro, The (Box 5)
  Publication City: Scranton, PA
- Metroscene (Metropolitcan Gay Style) (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, 1990s, Entertainment
  Publisher: Metroscene
- Metta (Box 5)
  Subject: Religious: Spirituality, HIV/ADIS, Religious: Buddhist, Gay, Lesbian, 1980s
  Publisher: Buddhist Association of the Gay and Lesbian Community
  Publication City: Bloomfield, NJ
- MGPC News (Massachusetts Gay Political Caucus, also known as Massacusetts Gay Political Caucus) (Box 5)
  Subject: Politics, 1990s, 1980s, Gay, Lesbian, HIV/AIDS
  Publisher: Massachusetts Gay & Lesbian Political Caucus (MGLPC)
- Mid-Hudson Valley AIDS Task Force (Box 5)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Health, Medicine
  Publisher: Mid-Hudson Valley AIDS Task Force
  Publication City: White Plains, NY
- Midtown Times, The (Box 5)
  Subject: 1990s, Gay, Lesbian, Community, News
  Publisher: Proton Enterprises, Ltd.
- Midwest Lobby Days Report (National Gay and Lesbian Task Force) (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Gay liberation movement, Politics, Legal, 1990s
  Publisher: National Gay and Lesbian Task Force
- Militant, The (A Socialist Newsweekly) (Box 5)
  Subject: Politics, Legal, Occupation Based Organizations, Labor
  Publisher: The Militant
- MILO National Weight Lifting Champion (Box 5)
  Subject: Physique, Men, Health, Catalog
  Publisher: Milo Bar Bell Co.
- Mineshaft, The (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, Men, Community, Cruising, Leather, Fetish, 1980s
  Publisher: The Mineshaft
- Ministry of Light (Box 5)
  Subject: Religious: Christian, Gay, Lesbian, HIV/AIDS, 1990s, Bisexual, Youth, Families
  Publisher: Ministry of Light
  Publication City: San Anselmo, CA
- Minnesota AIDS Project (Newsletter) (Box 5)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, 1980s
  Publisher: Minnesota AIDS Project
- Miriam's House Newsletter (A permanents home for homeless women living with AIDS and their children) (Box 5)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Women, Youth, Families, Community service
  Publisher: Miriam's House
- Mirror (Montreal) (Box 5)
  Subject: 1990s, Gay, Lesbian, Queer, News, Entertainment
  Publisher: Imprimeries Quebecor
- Mirror, The (New England) (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, 1980s, Lesbian, Alternative local newspaper, Classifieds, News
  Publisher: Entertainment Media, Inc.
- MN Gay and Lesbian Festival of Pride (Minnesota) (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Pride Parade and Events, 1980s
  Publisher: The Gay Pride Committee (Target City Coalition)
- MOCA Network Bulletin (Men of Color AIDS [MOCA] Prevention Program) (Box 5)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, People of Color, Men, Government Publication(s), Health, 1990s
  Publisher: Office of Gay & Lesbian Concerns, New York City Department of Health
- MOJA = Gay & Black (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, People of Color, African American, Race, 1970s, Gay liberation movement
- Monterey Lay Out (Box 5)
  Subject: 1970s, Gay, Lesbian, Entertainment, Community
  Publisher: L.H. & A.C. Enterprises
  Publication City: Carmel, CA
- Morning Due: Journal of Men Against Sexism (Box 5)
  Subject: Anti-sexist men, Men, Feminist, 1970s
  Publisher: Morning Due Collective (Seattle)
- Morning Star Metropolitan Community Church of Worcester (Newsletter) (Box 5)
  Subject: 1980s, Metropolitan Community Church, Gay, Lesbian, Religious, Religious: Christian
  Publisher: Metropolitan Community Church of Worcester
  Publication City: Worcester, MA
- Mothers' Voices (Speaking from the Heart about AIDS) (Box 5)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Families, Politics, Legal, 1990s, Health, Medicine
  Publisher: Mothers' Voices
- Movement Research Performance Journal (Box 5)
  Subject: Arts, Queer, Gay arts, Lesbian, Gay, Transgender, Gender issues, Drag, Performing arts, Transsexual, Transvestite, 1990s
  Publisher: Movement Research, Inc.
- MR (Manifest Reader) (Box 5)
  Subject: Gay, Leather, Erotica, Classifieds
  Publisher: Alternative Publishing Company
  Publication City: Forestville, CA
- Muff Divers (Box 5)
  Subject: Zine, Lesbian, Women, Feminist
- Music Women (A Newsletter Especially For Managers & Producers of Women's Music) (Box 5)
  Subject: Women, Music, Arts, 1970s, Feminist, Lesbian, Lesbian separatists
  Publisher: Sight & Sound Women
- My Tongue (A Journal of Yale Bisexual Gay Lesbian Awareness Days) (Box 5)
  Subject: 1990s, Yale University, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, College/University
  Publisher: My Tongue
  Publication City: New Haven, CT
- NAAPP Sack, The (National Alumni AIDS Prevention Project) (Box 6)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, College/University, Sefer sex, 1990s
  Publisher: Jackson State University National Alumni AIDS Prevention Project
  Publication City: Jackson, MS
- NABC Newsletter (National Association of Business Councils) (Box 6)
  Subject: Business, Occupation Based Organizations, Gay liberation movement, Politics, Gay, Lesbian, 1980s
  Publisher: National Association of Business Councils (NABC)
- Namesletter (Names Project Newsletter, Friends of the Quilt) (Box 6)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Community, Community service, 1990s, Television, Politics, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Heterosexual, Prisoners, Religious
  Publisher: The NAMES Project Foundation
- NASPA Network on Gay, Lesbian, & Bisexual Concerns Newsletter (formerly "Task Force") (Box 6)
  Subject: 1980s, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Gay liberation movement, Politics, Youth, Community service
  Publisher: Network on Gay, Lesbian, & Bisexual Concerns (NASPA)
- Nation, The (edited by Cornell alum Andrew Kopkind) (Box 6)
  Subject: Queer, Gay liberation movement, Politics, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, HIV/AIDS, People of Color, Gender issues, Cornell University, 1990s
  Publisher: The Nation Company, Inc.
- National Gay & Lesbian Task Force (NGLTF) Commemorative Booklet and Creating Change Conference Program 1988 (Box 6)
  Subject: NGLTF, Politics, Legal, Gay, Lesbian, Gay liberation movement, 1980s
  Publisher: National Gay & Lesbian Task Force (NGLTF)
- National Gay Health Directory, The (A Compendium of Health Services for Lesbians & Gay Men) (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay, Health, Directory, Lesbian, Safer sex, Medicine, 1970s
  Publisher: The National Gay Health Coalition Educational Foundation
- National Institute of Justice AIDS Bulletin (Box 6)
- National Queer Arts Festival (Box 6)
  Subject: Gay arts, Performing arts, Arts, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender, Queer, 2000s
  Publisher: Queer Culture Center
- NC Pride Newsletter (North Carolina Lesbian and Gay Pride) (Box 6)
  Subject: 1990s, Pride Parade and Events, Gay, Lesbian, Community
  Publisher: NC Pride (North Carolina Pride)
- NCBG Executive Director Reports (A Publication of the National Coalition of Black Gays, Inc.) (Box 6)
  Subject: People of Color, Gay, African American, 1980s, Race, Gay liberation movement, Politics, Legal
  Publisher: National Coalition of Black Gays, Inc.
- NCSSE News (National Coalition to Support Sexuality Education) (Box 6)
  Subject: Education, Safer sex, Heterosexual, Gay, Lesbian, Contraception, Legal, Health, Medicine, 1990s
  Publisher: National Coalition to Support Sexuality Education (NCSSE)
- Neighbors, The (Box 6)
- NetGALA (The Network of Gay/ Lesbian Alumni/ae Associations) (Box 6)
  Subject: College/University, Education, 1980s, 1990s, Harvard University
  Publisher: NetGALA (The Network of Gay and Lesbian Alumni/ae Assocations)
- Network News (Bay Area Network of Gay and Lesbian Educators) (Box 6)
- Network News (National Network) (Box 6)
  Subject: Youth, Unemployment, Politics, 1970s, Politics, Legal, Safer sex, Contraception